[
  {
    "question": "Which Planet Could You Not Walk On?",
    "a1": "Mars",
    "a2": "Jupiter",
    "a3": "Venus",
    "a4": "Mercury",
    "right": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "About How Old Is Our Solar System?",
    "a1": "About 14 Billion Years Old",
    "a2": "About 3.5 Billion Years Old",
    "a3": "About 4.5 Billion Years Old",
    "a4": "About 6 Billion Years Old",
    "right": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Far Is Pluto From The Sun?",
    "a1": "About 843 Million Miles",
    "a2": "About 2.93 Billion Miles",
    "a3": "About 103.4 Billion Miles",
    "a4": "About 3.67 Billion Miles",
    "right": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Much Larger Is Olympus Mons Compared To Mount Everest?",
    "a1": "Three Times",
    "a2": "Two Times",
    "a3": "Five Times",
    "a4": "Twelve Times",
    "right": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Many Known Moons Does Jupiter Have?",
    "a1": "71",
    "a2": "79",
    "a3": "56",
    "a4": "83",
    "right": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "About How Wide Are Saturn's Main Rings From One End To Another?",
    "a1": "About 39,000 Miles",
    "a2": "About 34,000 Miles",
    "a3": "About 49,000 Miles",
    "a4": "About 47,000 Miles",
    "right": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Percentage Of All Solar System Mass Does The Sun Contain?",
    "a1": "99.86%",
    "a2": "87.13%",
    "a3": "92.42%",
    "a4": "72.66%",
    "right": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Much Longer Is The Sun Expected To 'Burn' As It Does Today?",
    "a1": "About 3 Billion Years",
    "a2": "About 12 Billion Years",
    "a3": "About 7 Billion Years",
    "a4": "About 5 Billion Years",
    "right": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Greek Word 'Planetes' Is The Origin Of 'Planet', What Does It Mean?",
    "a1": "Bright",
    "a2": "Sky",
    "a3": "Wonderer",
    "a4": "Goddess",
    "right": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Much Further Is The Edge Of The Solar System Compared To Pluto?",
    "a1": "About 120 Times",
    "a2": "About 1,000 Times",
    "a3": "About 3,200 Times",
    "a4": "About 630 Times",
    "right": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Planet Has The Largest Ocean?",
    "a1": "Jupiter",
    "a2": "Earth",
    "a3": "Neptune",
    "a4": "Saturn",
    "right": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Planets Are The 'Terrestrial' Planets?",
    "a1": "Earth, Jupiter, Saturn, Neptune",
    "a2": "Mars, Earth, Venus, Mercury",
    "a3": "Mars, Jupiter, Neptune, Saturn",
    "a4": "Venus, Mars, Saturn, Pluto",
    "right": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is The Second Largest Planet In Our Solar System?",
    "a1": "Uranus",
    "a2": "Neptune",
    "a3": "Jupiter",
    "a4": "Saturn",
    "right": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Many Dwarf Planets Can Be Found In Our Solar System?",
    "a1": "One",
    "a2": "Two",
    "a3": "Five",
    "a4": "Twelve",
    "right": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Many Earth Days Is Equivalent To One Day On Venus?",
    "a1": "12 Earth Day",
    "a2": "243 Earth Days",
    "a3": "365 Earth Days",
    "a4": "59 Earth Days",
    "right": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is The Largest Asteroid In The Inner Solar System?",
    "a1": "7 Iris",
    "a2": "1 Ceres",
    "a3": "3 Juno",
    "a4": "2 Pallas",
    "right": "2"
  }
]